# Wisdom okorie

wisdomokorie18@gmail.com 09037208206 Becareful Lodge Ishieke, Ebonyi

#### **Summary**

I love to code!!

I'm wisdom okorie by name, I'm a fullstack developer with the following skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, bootstrap, React js, Node js, Express js, MongoDB, API. i have worked on alot of projects which also include changing and converting the templet of an already built website and building cool projects from stretch too.

#### **Experience**

## Full Stack web Developer

Closeseller • Lagos Nigeria 05/2023 - Present

I built and designed this wonderful business website from stretch with react js and it's responsive too.

### Full Stack web Developer

Closeseller • Lagos Nigeria 05/2023 - Present

I built and designed this wonderful business website from stretch with react is and it's responsive too.

### Web Developer

wisdom personal portfolio • Abakiliki Ebonyi state nigeria 01/2023 - Present

This is my personal portfolio and I sampled some of the project I have worked on here

# Web Developer Internship

Shinarium • Ebonyi state university

01/2022 - Present

I worked on an already made html, CSS and JavaScript templet and made it look absolutely different.

worked on a project which include changing and converting the templet of an already built website

#### Skills

Javascript, Communication skills, GIT, CSS, Html5, ReactJS, MongoDB, Node.js, Express.js, GitHub, APIS

#### **Education**

# Computer science

Ebonyi State University • Abakiliki Ebonyi state nigeria 05/2023